[♪♪♪]
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
[WIND WHISTLING]
[SAMWELL SHIVERING]
NORTHMAN 1: Oi!
NORTHMAN 2: Mind out.
Move!
[♪♪♪]
[MEN CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
NORTHMAN: Look, on the west wall!
SOLDIER: Get down to the crypt!
[BABY CRYING]
SOLDIER: Just hold.
MAN: We'll take him.
- Come on, help the lads!
- SOLDIER 1: Yes, my lady.
LYANNA: Quickly, now! Quickly!
Get those in position.
- SOLDIER 1: Come on.
- SOLDIER 2: Close the gate!
SOLDIER 3: That's it.
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTS]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
[GASPS SOFTLY]
[DRAGON ROARING]
[SOLDIERS SHOUTING
INDISTINCTLY]
[HORSES SNORTING]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Oh, for fuck's sake.
You took your time.
[HORSE NEIGHS]
[SNORTING]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[DRAGONS GROWLING]
[♪♪♪]
Do you speak their tongue?
Tell them to lift their swords.
[WIND WHISTLING]
[SPEAKS IN DOTHRAKI]
[WEAPONS CLINKING]
[♪♪♪]
[SPEAKING IN HIGH VALYRIAN]
[SOLDIERS EXCLAIMING]
[♪♪♪]
Valar morghulis.
Valar dohaeris.
Open the gate!
SOLDIER 1: Open the gate!
SOLDIER 2: Open the gate!
MAN 1:Come. Come on.
Easy.
[♪♪♪]
There's no need to execute me,
Ser Davos.
I'll be dead before the dawn.
[♪♪♪]
[SOLDIER SHOUTING
INDISTINCTLY]
[DOTHRAKI ULULATING]
SOLDIER [IN DOTHRAKI]: _
[WIND WHISTLING]
[HOOFBEATS POUNDING]